technicoz.com 2015-11-22

# Privacy Policy

The privacy of our visitors to TechniCoz.com is important to us.  
This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by TechniCoz.com and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, TechniCoz.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and a number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

#### DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on TechniCoz.com.Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to TechniCoz.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site

## **Comments Policy**

The author does not assume responsibility for comments he did not make on this blog. While comments are welcome from anybody, we reserve the right to remove any comment that is not deemed suitable for publication. This could include but is not limited to objectional and abusive comments. Hate, racist comments, or any other form of prejudice will be removed and the poster will be banned!  
Comments made for sole purpose of getting backlinks or advertising your/any product will not be accepted. Link to third party website will require moderation and we reserve the rights to edit/delete such links.  
Spam in any form will not be accepted and will be deleted immediately. We may take action against such spammers.  
Copyrights  
Supreme caution has been taken to make sure that there are no copyright infringements in terms of the multimedia content and the subject matter that is posted in this blog. If you find anything that could be considered a violation of the copyright norms, please contact me immediately.

Copyright © 2015.TechniCoz All Rights Reserved.
